<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mushroom Technology</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="reishi_intro">Reishi Mushroom also known as Lingzhi mushroom. Scientificly known as Ganoderma Lucidum.
        Sheng Nong: Father of Chineese medicine kept this mushroom in the category of superior herbs in his book. Reishi is used as medicine in comman. Reishi has lot
        of health benefits like it acts as anti viral, it helps to cure lungs diseases like asthma, it is also helpful in
        Stomach ulcers, Liver disease, Kidney disease, Allergy, Diabetes mellitus, Insomnia, Altitude sickness, Chronic fatigue syndrome.
        It has the properties of anti cancer also. \n
        <b>Nutritional Values:-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="oyster_intro">Oyster Mushroom is comman exmaple of mushroom after button mushroom. Scientific name of oyster
    is Pleurotus. This is also known as Dhingri in India. These mushrooms has great nutritional values. This is a good source of
        diatry protein and food. This mushroom was first cultivated by Flank in German in 1917. It is grown almost all over the world
        due to its pleasent flavour, long shelf live and simple cultivation methods.\n
        <b>Nutritional Values:-</b>
    </string>
    <string name="button_intro">Button Mushroom is the most comman type of Mushroom and is also known as Comman Mushroom.
    Scientific name for button mushroom is Agaricus Bisporus and this mushroom is native to grasslands in Europe and North America.
        Agaricus is a genus of mushrooms containing both edible and poisonous species, with possibly over 300 members worldwide. It is a fungus. It originated in Brazil,
        but is now grown in China, Japan, and Brazil for sale. A solution containing chemicals that are taken from the plant (extract) is used as medicine.
        Agaricus mushroom contains chemicals that might improve the body use of insulin and decrease insulin resistance in people with type 2 diabetes. Some developing
        research also suggests it might be able to strengthen the immune system, fight tumor development, and work as an antioxidant.
        About 17 species of Agaricus have been reported from India. It is commonly known as kukurmutta in U.P. and dhingri in Punjab. A. campestris (field mushroom),
        A. bisporus (A. brunnescence; white mushroom) are common edible mushrooms. A. bisporus (cultivated mushroom) is widely cultivated for food purposes in Solan
        (Himachal Pradesh). Some species of Agaricus are poisonous (e.g., A. xanthoderma) and some species may cause gastrointestinal disturbances in some persons
        (e.g., A. placomyces, A. silvaticus).\n
        Nutritional Values:-\n

    </string>
    <string name="button_cult">Mushrooms are considered to be heterotrophic (saprophytic) organisms and thus possess no chlorophylls, but decompose organic materials to feed off.
        Agaricus bisporus can be cultivated on various lignocellulosic materials. Growing and cultivation of this species has succeeded on different composted organic such as chicken,
        horse or pigeon manures, straw residues from  wheat, oat, tifton and reed crops corn. Cultivation of Agaricus bisporus (button mushroom) and its usages in the biosynthesis of
        nanoparticles. Button Mushrooms does not require light. But it is not necessary that the mushrooms should be grown in dark environment.
        The benefit of growing them in dark is that the moisture content can easily be preserved in dark. Button mushrooms need temperature of 55-60F.
        They need a high relative humidity.
    </string>
    <string name="shiitake_intro">Shiitake mushroom is edible mushroom and is native to East Asia, which is cultivated and consumed in many
        Asian countries.It is considered as medicinal mushroom also. The Scientific name for this mushroom is Lentinula Edodes. Shiitake normally
        grows on the trees or woods which are decaying. Its natural distribution includes warm and moist weather.\n
        Nutrition Values:-


    </string>
    <string name="reishi_clut">Reishi Mushroom is found infrequently in nature, and that is why this mushroom is highly chrished and expensive.
        In ancient times in China, the person who used to find and pick reishi mushrooms, was given good rewards and high rank officials job.
        It was first cultivated by man in 1970. The most comman method for cultivating reishi are Wood Log Cultivation Method, Short Wood Segment
        Method, Tree Stump Cultivation Method, Sawdust bag Cultivation Method and Bottle Cultivation Method. Optimal temperature for growth
        of this mushroom is 25-28 degree C, and Carbondioxide content should be around 600ppm. And Relative Humidity should be around 80-85%.
    </string>

    <string name="shitake_cult">
        Shiitake, Lentinula edodes, is a saprophyte and white rot fungus which feeds on dead oak tree species in nature. In its life cycle, each basidium under the gill of a fruit
         body produces four basidiospores which sporulate under a certain condition to become a primary mycelium and then a secondary mycelium by fusion
        between compatible mycelia. Shiitake spawn is a medium, colonized by the secondary mycelia. The secondary mycelia will eventually form fruit bodies.
        Ideal temperature for shiitake is 21-27 degree C. Ideal relative humidity is 95-100%.
    </string>
    <string name="oyster_cult">
        The ideal temperature of oyster is 24-25 degree C. The relative humidity content should be around 85-95%.
        It should be grown under controlled conditions and in dark environment. The things you require for this are straw, container,
        oyster mushroom spawn, gas burner, a dark room with maintained temperature conditions.
    </string>
</resources>
